Of course, I'll always be with you
I'll always be with you, I'll always be with you
So you're happy, and you feel it if you can't wait
I'll always be with you in my dreams
It's a day like this, so I'm going to pick it up
You and you and you
If the eyes of your hands meet with each other
Don't hurt each other, because love can't be helped
I can't even imagine how I feel
Ah ah ah ah
Yes!
What a joke!
The answer is a question!
Your assistant is still there.
Not now.
Is it her?
Hey, who are you?
This is the building.
You can't find a room for a while.
Yeah, it's the building.
It's just a kitchen.
Who's there?
He's there!
Let's go!
I'm going to destroy you!
What is it?
There is no danger.
I'm going to destroy you!
What? That's Chizuakusaku!
I want to get out of here!
I don't want to see Tsugata.
Chizuakusaku?
If I were to get knocked out, I would have gone.
Maybe I would have gone to my house too?
I want to get out of here!
Chizuakusaku is the person who has collected my money and money for the whole world!
Do you want to get involved with the world?
I will get a loan from both ways and eventually send it to you.
I will use the money to take the money out of my pocket and then let everyone get into trouble.
Everyone, your money is very cheap and expensive, isn't it?
Idiot!
It's all over the place!
How many years, how many years, and how many years have you been living?
I wonder if I'll be able to tell you the truth.
I have to tell you the truth.
I'll be able to tell you the truth.
Oroza Hime!
It's better to tell the truth in the future than to know the truth.
If this is the way to make things happen again,
what's the matter, Oroza Hime?
What's the matter, Hime?
Do you mean that I'm telling you?
Oji...
Oji! It's not me, Mr. Hime!
I'm a law enforcement officer!
Mr. Hime doesn't say anything to you, he's not a law enforcement officer!
I'm not!
You're a law enforcement officer!
Mr. Hime, I'm a law enforcement officer!
Read it with your own name and name, Hime-sama, this is it!
It's so beautiful!
Then, Bun-dai, what did you do here?
I heard that there are a lot of animals, animals that are interested in humans, and animals that live together.
I don't even have a hand, and I can't say anything.
Why can't I say anything?
I thought I wouldn't be able to answer the question.
Why?
There is no reason why humans and animals are together!
There is no reason to be able to live together!
Here are the animals that live together.
Bun-dai, there is no reason to be able to answer the question.
I'll never forget that!
Hello! I'm Sharadako.
This is Hime-ji.
Have you seen Ueba?
I just recently went to a country school.
I don't even know about the country school.
That's right!
Ueba-san was actually mad at me.
She's mad at me.
Hey, wait!
I'm afraid. If you get ready, you'll have no time.
What? You mean such a fool?
It's a pink rose.
It's cute, isn't it?
It's just like my head, isn't it?
Where did you get it from?
Did you get it from Shizuakushaku?
Shizuakushaku?
That's right. Shizuakushaku is here.
Oh, my God!
Robin!
Oh, did you get it from Shizuakushaku?
Oh, what?
Oh, what are you doing?
Huh?
What's that?
I'm going to get it. It's a pink rose.
Shizuakushaku, isn't it?
Did you get it from me?
The body is like this, but the body is like this.
It's me.
It's me!
It's a pink rose.
I'm going to use it often.
Everyone is doing it well.
Wait.
Why are you doing this to me?
It's me!
It's the first time I've ever seen such a thing.
Look at my head.
Now I'm going to die.
I'm going to die.
I'm going to forget that I'm going to die.
Soko, are you going to die?
I'm going to die.
How is it going?
It's up to you.
It's really a big deal.
It's a huge deal.
We'll get it.
It's up to you.
You're doing this to me.
It's a big deal.
Oh, and that's it.
It's still a place where the war is still happening in the world.
The war didn't come out at the time.
Even if it was still there, it won't be destroyed.
You're such a human being.
Oh?
Oh, it's a promise.
Oh, right.
It's a great honor.
Let's give it a try.
Mom!
Don't you think it's a honor?
What's wrong with you?
You can't do bad things, right?
I'm not that bad, but let's just let it go.
Hahaha!
As I was, I was born as a member of the Minami Shima tribe.
Wow! I've had a lot of challenges.
Besides, there are a lot of sand and grass, concrete and iron.
And if you're born an item and you're born an item, you have to raise your sister.
Really?
But I think I've done a great job.
Haku-saku.
This Ashienba-Hawaru-Kan-gubun-dai
is the third-generation of Yushirai-Setou-na-Key-Fuomatsu
in the history of Yushirai-Setou-na-Key-Fuomatsu.
I'll do my best until I do my best.
Hey, hey!
Don't talk too much!
If you say that,
I'll say that you're beautiful, and I'll say that you're beautiful!
I loved the beautiful, but
I didn't expect that you would be surprised
by the fact that you're a beautiful woman!
Yaaaaaaay!
Let's go!
The first time Hime-sama and Haji-methe loved each other
was that she had a bad habit of getting a pig's head and head
and that's the reason behind this.
The princess of the Balachizu-na-Key-Fuomatsu
was born to be a real princess of a royal family.
Balachizu...
At that time, I was so proud that
I was born to be the princess who was born to be a princess
who was born to be a royal family of a royal family of a royal family.
I heard something, it's so noisy.
Really?
It's a bandit!
Oh, I see.
It's been a while since I've been to the Ueba.
No, no, no.
What's wrong?
It's a bandit.
I feel like I'm in a hurry.
Are you in a hurry?
Am I in a hurry?
No, no.
Then,
My turn!
I'm full!
Nothing is now!
No!
It's a birthday cake.
It's good that I ate it and thought it was a lot of it.
What?
No.
It's a joke.
Huh?
What are you doing?
I've got a lot of people involved in this.
Goji.
What?
Took the disaster helmet.
Why so many stuff?
Yeah, yeah.
What do I do with
I'm sure that I'll eat it in a Russian blood syrup.
A Russian blood syrup?
I'm sure it'll be good.
Even if you eat it, I can't cry any more.
Please don't tell me that I'm not going to be a Russian blood syrup.
I wouldn't forgive the sudden incident that Russia is making.
Russia? Russia is more likely to be a Russian blood syrup.
What?
That's why Russia and Russia are both strong.
You're the one I love!
You've got no sense!
You're the one I hate!
You have to leave me to the end to make me fall for you!
Shut up!
I got no sense!
Stop it!
What are you doing?
I... I'm...
Stop it!
What's wrong?
You're just giving me a small round of applause.
You done it right!
I ate his stomach because he wanted to eat my stomach, so...
I ate his stomach so I ate his stomach.
My stomach was delicate, you know.
The big deck board is different from the ones you saw.
What kind of deck board is that?
What?
I forgot to do it.
My stomach!
You're doing something?
I'll be able to do it for you!
Huh? The war has begun.
Yeah!
I'm not going to give up the war until this end.
No, it's not.
That's it!
Everyone, follow me!
Oh, wait!
It's not a war!
Huh?
What's going on?
What was that for?
Well, if we can't do a war anymore than a war, I am not a war.
I am not a war.
That's it!
Not a war, but a war between strong like Titan, I am not a war.
No, this isn't it.
This isn't it.
Hey, this is it.
You just have to hold on and wait for it.
Robyn is here.
Gona come over here.
Kyunkide's here.
I'll protect Hijime here.
It's not a war.
It's not like that.
My mission is to make a world together.
However, if you get a chance to fight,
you won't get a chance to fight Yuki Sakiyaki and Hime-san.
This is a tough fight.
I'm so happy to see you.
What are you talking about?
You don't have to fight like this.
Why are you fighting like this?
I'm so happy.
Aren't you fighting like this?
That's how it is.
You have to talk if you get hurt.
You can come back home.
If I'm singer, I'll do it on me.
I don't want to do that.
I'll do my best anyway.
I'm not afraid of being so close to you.
But I can't do that.
What?
It's more than one hit!
It's a hit!
You're a bad man! You're a bad man!
You're a bad man!
What are you doing?
Handcuff!
Yes!
I don't do anything!
I'm here!
Oh no!
Yes!
You're a fool!
I'm going to be a good guy!
I'll teach you what to do!
Everyone, let's go!
Oh!
I'm sorry!
Everyone, let's go!
Please stop!
What's going on?
I'm sorry!
Wait! You're in a team fight!
This is a battle between a man and a man with a heart.
A battle between a person and a man with a heart?
This is the time to get rid of this man and slay me.
Yes!
To protect you from danger, you'll be destroyed.
And you'll be destroyed by your own eyes!
Ah!
Oh, no!
Everyone, stop!
Stop!
Ah!
What's going on?
Huh?
Why are you doing so much?
I see.
I thought you were a real father.
What?
What did we do?
I don't know why.
What?
The map is a suspicious one.
The teacher of that magic is coming from us.
What?
The things that we are doing in the world of our hearts!
My father!
What is the reason for that?
Well, that's...
...the spirit.
The spirit...
What?
You're stupid!
You're not a bad person.
No, no, no.
We are bad people.
That's right.
I mean, I'm not a bad person.
I'm not a bad person.
Everyone, stop!
Hey!
Stop!
Oh!
Uda!
Be careful!
My promise is over.
This world has come to an end.
What are you saying?
Be careful!
You guys...
...could be hurt.
If there's a reason for that...
...the teacher of the magic is going to disappear.
I want to disappear...
...in the end of your life.
No!
Don't disappear yet!
I'm not going to be a bad person...
...in the world after all.
Don't worry.
Even if I die...
...the people of the world...
...will continue to fight.
Oh, no!
It was a lie.
You always protect the sky.
You're an evil person.
I'm here to fight you.
My dear.
Your great brother...
...there's no one to hide from you.
No one can...
...just like you can do it freely.
Your heart is filled with joy.
That kind of heart can't make you see...
...the teacher of magic.
Hey!
You're so stupid!
I'm so stupid!
So...
I won't let you go.
I'm so stupid.
I can't believe you're still alive.
I'm sorry, Shimei.
I'm sorry.
I've started to fight with you until the end of the fight.
You need your help.
Let's go together.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Shimei.
I'm sorry, everyone.
I'm sorry.
I can't believe you're still alive.
I've met you all the time.
I'm sorry, everyone!
No matter who, no matter who, it's still the same
Let's go home early
There's always a song
Let's sing the song
I'm singing here
No matter who, no matter who, it's still the same
Nothing will fit until now
There's always a place ahead I wish it had an agreement
That I wouldn't have been born
Fajia, fajia, fajia, fajia, fajia, fajia, fajia, fajia
Piss! Piss! Piss! Piss! Piss! Piss! Piss! Piss! Piss! Piss! Piss! Piss! Piss! Piss!
Let's go, let's see, it's not fun.
Hey, come here, let's have fun!
Let's go, let's go to the hot spring!
Hey, Muka Muka
what should we do for the world's most fun?
Uya, Uya, Uya!
I was going to send a signal to Tsuru-san in front of me, but I don't know what's going to happen to this island.
Uya, Uya!
Huh? What's going on here?
Is this the future?
Next time, I'll be with you, Uya, Uya, Uya, Uya!